Hello everyone. Com
hope I am live. Uh, okay.
Better check is going well.
Wait.
Uh,
what the Yeah, today I will be checking
if my stream uh internet is working well
or not. We'll be playing a little bit of
uh Warox a little bit.
I do have some other stuff I have to
work on and like finish some task. So,
I'll
probably be uh playing Warogs a little
bit today and then try to
uh finish some of the task I have.
Today will be like a network test
thingy. Do I do um
do I do be uh what do you call it?
though I do be testing some of the
things and like
um
testing off stream by not going live to
platforms but I've been like betray
testing lately and it has been stable
on 4G connection.
If I switch my connection of my Wi-Fi
from 5G to 4G, it's more stable.
Some more of testing it while playing
Warogs like a online game. [music] And
uh yeah,
give me a minute. I'll just
uh wrap up things and
we go into the game.
Uh
that should do it. And let me switch to
the game.
You must uh
uh you see it.
You see it? Don't see it. And there.
Nice.
Let's hope this works.
Uh hope
uh hope this works out.
Give me a minute.
McDonald's on stream award
and uh this thing has to be go live have
to like close my
game Start. It did start.
>> I got [__] to do.
>> It did start. Hey.
So, I'm a bit running out of Oh, not
that.
I'm a bit running out of like stuff.
Rather magazines. I'll just take a lot
of magazines really.
And um take
Uh this guy
and this
and that's deeper.
score.
>> Wait, I forgot about a shot.
>> What?
I don't know. I did optimize the
optimized a little bit of the
not like
graphics of the game. So you will see no
shadows. It's literally potato mode.
All right.
It came through.
Let me double check my FPS on my
stuff.
Uh,
this should be better.
I thought I could
wait
my audio
here.
Let's go. Thank you for waiting.
Hello, Solar Ram. Welcome.
Hello. Hello. Hope you're doing well.
Do let me know if my internet is working
well cuz it should be fine.
So smooth. No, it is.
Wait, the stream is smooth. Yeah. Oh my
god. First time I'm here and I heard
that.
It's actually pretty nice.
Ah, my game,
bro.
My game is stuck,
brother. What is going on?
Thank you so much.
Oh my god, that guy waited for me and he
landed me perfectly
just cuz I was lagged out.
Helicopter is rising like that and the
flying like that is rising my heart
rate.
Isn't that a man?
Oh my god, they're like
Oh my god.
Where? This guy.
Well, another attack helicopter.
Enemy vehicle taken out.
Bro, what is happening?
Damn. What was that?
Never in
man. People are aggressive now, huh?
Oh [__]
we have an intruder.
Bro, what the [__] was that? What the
hell was that?
Why are they attacking like that?
One helicopter in a Humvey with an
attacker on top. What?
What is happening?
Why? Why are they so
so so
aggressive? The another helicopter. Oh
my god.
Oh my god, they're here.
A
bro,
bro, come on. What is going on?
What is this?
It's ramming people. It's killing
people.
this.
I don't get it. Why are they [__] on
blue team?
This helicopter.
I want to kill that
uh Humvey guy
somehow.
and steal their Humvey somehow. The the
trick to kill an Humvey is to hit their
weak point. That's the wheels.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. They're they're
coming. They're coming.
I need a RPG.
Okay. Someone actually killed it. Crazy,
bro.
Thank you.
Bro, someone stole my guns. [__]
Oh, thank you for healing me for free.
Another helicopter,
bro.
Is that a bird with a rocket?
That is That is a void with a rocket.
Oh my lord. Holy mould
you ever do another jockathons or
something similar? I could
uh if I'm able to
I'll just farm money from reviving these
guys.
I could if I could a I'm able to, but
I'm not able to stream for 24 hours 24
hours now cuz I got school, I got work,
I have to be an responsible adult now.
I do wish to
If the opportunity arises,
I could do something smaller kind.
So now I could do some something of a
small kind.
I could do something small of a kind.
Why do you say that? Like you were
disappointed.
Yeah, because uh
I wish I could. Huh?
What
did he just team kill?
I I I wish I could just stream all the
time, but I can't.
That's why I
Ah, I see another guy.
Am I heavy? I am heavy.
I have a lot of grenades.
I have seven grenades.
Yeah, if another Humvey comes, I'm going
to
I'm going to steal some.
Oh, what the
There's an SP.
How's this all? How has your day been?
It's been a while, huh?
How's everything?
How's life?
Oh my god. Another helicopter.
Is this a glitch?
I feel like this is a glitch.
How many?
My brother is in the hospital. Oh no.
What happened?
Hope he's okay and safe.
Gets better.
Wait, this is a glitch, isn't it? It's
infinitely duplicating.
No, there's it.
I see you. I see you. I see you.
Is this infinitely duplicating?
Ah, my game is
my game.
Good guess.
Yeah, someone just sniped her.
At least I don't have to share around
for a few days.
Look how blue team guys are here.
But do you feel lonely that you're alone
or something like that
is logged? enemy.
Where?
I see enemy incoming in front of me.
Hold on.
His armor was crazy.
Oh, his armor was crazy.
>> Hostile little bird above us.
An enemy.
Where?
Huh?
>> Sorry. Sorry. I thought you were enemy.
It's all right.
>> Okay. Okay.
Oh my god. No way. I killed my own team.
Friendly kill. Oh [screaming]
[groaning]
[__] No.
[__] The an actual enemy came in.
Ah, he died. No,
this claim considering we we already
avoided each other.
Ah,
>> vehicle destroyed. No further movement.
>> Man, what do I do?
I shouldn't have killed my teammate. O,
there were two people enemy.
Wow.
Get out of there.
Charming personalities. Come back any
time.
No pilot.
It's not going to take a a stranger.
How about
Wait, did you just donate?
Oh, hey, Solar. Why did you donate?
Hey, thank you. You didn't have to.
What?
Huh?
Did you just What?
Wait, what? What did you Huh?
I got bored. The nani, use your money
for yourself.
Oh my god. Let me check. How much was
it?
Five. And I barely check my thingy.
I forgot I had a qualifi.
Oh my god. Crazy.
I don't know what to put here.
Here you go. Joke. Have a good night. A
thank you. Thank you for the $1.
Thank you.
where there's no one at.
These guys are going mechanical mode.
Going with the attack helicopters.
That was a prepaid car that expires in 5
months.
Don't waste your money though. Keep
give value to money. Use it for yourself
and stuff. But thank you for using
a little bit of it towards me. Thank
you. Really means a lot. Appreciate the
thought.
Oh my god, the truck.
The truck.
Okay,
Mexico.
So far, the stream has been smoother,
right?
That's really rare.
You want honestly so rare.
Also, I wasn't expecting you to find out
that quickly. Oh, because Twitch now, if
you do a donation,
um Twitch uh chat, I had linked Kofi
with my Twitch chat. So, I get the
alert. So, I got the alert from Twitch
chat. I'm multi streaming now.
Normally it's supposed to send it on
YouTube chat,
but it's send on Twitch for some reason.
Hello,
how you doing?
How was your stream? I did watch a
little bit of your stream.
It was buffering a little bit
towards the end, right?
You were on mobile data the show.
What?
Oh my god. Roku, thank you for the tier
one subscription. Oh my, bro. Don't
waste your money.
Damn.
You've been subscribed for 25 months.
Crazy.
How's the Roku Chan doing? Hello. Hello.
Ro, you should definitely play this
game. It is so fun.
It was good. I fell asleep after my
stream. Ah,
should I help him build?
I forgot about cards and I was like, you
start streaming, I'll take it away from
next month. You start streaming. Uh
30 minutes cuz I forgot about the cards
and I was like you saw social
go
I mean ever since I came to Japan I've
been active now. I just wish I can get
my uh PC from back home to here so I can
use it as my streaming setup streaming
PC.
So it will be too super lighter on the
laptop now. I'm wanting to do that
recently.
Oh, airplane. H.
That's a helicopter with minigun
box. So, yeah. SW dogs on stream steam.
Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep.
It is fun. It's like you can do so many
support things.
You can be a pilot. You can be a Uber
guy. You can be a air Uber. You can be
the Bob the Builder. Then you can be the
medic guy. You can be the scouter, the
recon.
Um,
get money.
That's a Humvey.
Okay,
there's people there.
That's our base. No.
Playing with no shadows is really nice.
I had to config so many stuff in the
in-game files in game config just to do
this. I hear gunshots.
North.
North. Where? Where? Where? I just saw
sniper.
Oh, base.
How is he? I've been good. D, I've been
good. I've been good.
I took a bath. I'm I'm ganky.
I took a bath. Damn. Gina,
my audio just died. What?
Hey, wait. My audio just died.
Huh?
What the?
Wait, I don't hear anything. What?
What
the hell?
What the voice? What happened to you?
Uh, of course that
live
laptop speaker does this die. Uh
what
happened to my PC
voice m okay
always try to fix it.
Uh,
one
nothing though. I don't get it.
Find your donation page on Google fairly
easily.
You famous? I found your donation page
on Google fairly easil.
Huh?
What page did you see?
Okay.
Wait, my audio died
there.
My audio just died.
Oh, camp over here.
Wait, why the hell is my
What happened to my speaker? Huh?
fairly easily. Which donation page was
was it actually?
Tell me.
>> [groaning]
>> over here. Down over here.
>> Okay. What the We have the same like
sentence clicks.
What?
What? Likes and dislikes.
>> Oh, my website
>> over here.
But it's okay.
I wish today was the day I didn't have
to worry about technical issues, but
bro,
honestly, bro,
>> I saw it said page under construction.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, it is.
Yeah,
she
H check one. Is it working?
What?
Wait, do I have to restart my stream,
you know, PC to fix my audio?
I don't get it.
I really don't get it.
I really, really don't get it.
What?
Ah, fixed it. Audio.
Also, this uh I need to repair the
make. Where's the fob? Where's the fob?
Why is this not supplied?
I I called I killed him.
Kill the one guy.
Um
Oh my god.
>> Under the third helicopter. No, that's
>> Yeah, I have to update that website. I
have to I was supposed to do it. That's
why I was I was wanting to do after the
stream, today's stream. I wanted to like
work on some of the things.
Well, thank you for the donation.
Wait,
did you just
have a good night, Jo? Hi.
Take care. Solar.
Thank you once again
for your kindness.
Oh god, there's enemies inside.
That is not a bad idea.
Is it over?
I killed them.
Let's go.
I'm going 15k.
Crazy.
The person who built this, I'm so happy.
I'm I'm glad
Don't yell, please. Hi. I want to let
too. Thank you again.
Have a good night, Solar.
Thank you again for coming by now and
talking with me. It means a lot.
That's cover.
[screaming]
What? How did he die?
That's good.
Oh my god, We're invincible.
I got you.
Nothing's coming to our radar. Come on.
I need money.
Where?
Oh my god. Bro, bro, bro, bro.
It went.
It went so fast. Dooo.
Dooo.
Uh,
why am I moving with my mouse? I can
just use AD left, right?
I never knew.
What is this guy saying? I can't
understand.
Oh my got me and I
got so
you
as inflators
spies. Guys,
Hello.
Welcome. Welcome.
Where is it? I can't see because of
these stupid trees.
Wish we could cut trees.
Ah,
that'll literally become Fortnite.
How you doing?
>> I'm doing great.
Hello. Hello.
Hope you're doing well.
>> I figured out how to fix my internet.
Now it's uh low latency the show. Good
quality too. Like okay quality
but network has no issues.
Where? Where? Where? Oh.
Ah, they started to molter us.
Where is it?
Molter.
Someone's motoring us. Doing okay. Way
back from work. I'm on the way back from
work. Ah, get on safe,
bro. Crazy.
How far away was that?
Remind me quick. Got to kill those
helicopters.
>> [groaning]
[screaming]
>> going to be sitting in the metro for an
hour. Ah,
come.
These guys are dying trying to revive
me.
Ah, my Sam is gone.
Yeah, it's nothing.
Maybe they got tired of our pew pew
to the point that he's like,
"Don't worry.
Let's go kill them.
Let's go. Pilot level four. Let's go."
Crazy.
And then there.
Holy god, the molter. Ah, I died.
Crazy.
[__] coming.
>> Revive me.
>> Thank you. Thank you, Shisha.
I I died again.
Wow.
I died again. Wow.
Somebody got me.
Oh my god.
>> Man down over here.
Thank you.
Oh god. Okay.
No one has a good gun.
The ones who died.
We got bombs and stuff, but that's not
enough.
Okay, I'm going to use this
I think they marked everything.
Where the
Yeah, those guys marked everything where
everything is. Are these porters from
those team? The green team? Yeah,
thank you.
Aha, the game is lagging.
Is this
uh
This is why I need a This is This is the
exact reason why I need a second PC.
I cannot survive.
Everything is in low settings
and I cannot survive.
Where are they?
I'm approaching your position.
What the hell?
Damn, we got a revive revor
with a defib.
I feel like he would be making so like a
bank of money.
Ah, these snipers
over here.
They're uh they're on there. Yeah,
they'll get a money for reviving and
doing anything in the game.
You get money and with that money you
buy load out guns etc.
[groaning]
Oh, this is mine right? I tried to hit
this
the game.
Feel like my RAM is the issue.
Can't do anything about that. Wow.
Too
laggy.
>> Honestly though, no. Like I was testing
while not streaming to any platform, but
it was streaming
and
it was not like this. This bad.
That's why I don't get it. None there.
No one's picking me up.
>> The [__] got me.
>> I'm literally up top. Come on.
Get me up.
So the thing is right now green team and
red team are sending their molters all
the way from their base so far away to
blue team. This is just sad.
It's a green team which has the upper
advantage. They're having
57 points
and they're literally destroying us.
Oh my god.
No one's reviving me. What the hell?
>> Get me up.
>> I give you $400. Doesn't remind me.
They're like spamming the Maltar.
Wow. I know you can
cancel the animation and send three
moltars by pressing C.
Then you fire a malt. You press C. Then
you fire again another moltar. Press C.
You can fire three moltars in a safe
spot.
They're doing that thing. That's why
it's non-stop.
They're reviving everyone except me.
None there.
A He died.
Yeah,
like I should uh reset.
I have a have a hope that someone is
going to revive,
but they're getting sniped from this
trace over here.
Uh
will you come? I'm giving your money
though.
Someone's coming.
No,
>> bro. Don't give me a false hope. Wait,
wait. Someone's actually waving
up and revive. Please. I'm literally
behind you.
I'm literally behind you. Please,
bro.
Bro, what the hell,
guys? Come on. Just Just get up the
platform.
Okay, someone is here.
Don't tell me he's looting me. Ah,
someone looted my stuff.
Took you long enough. Thank you.
Brah
died in front of him.
Yuck again.
Thank you.
I don't have any heals.
What?
Ah, the def guy.
Bro, he's making so much money though.
I'm 100% sure
he would be making so much money.
They have a freaking tank over there.
Holy lord.
What is this game?
They have tank. They have
spam molter. Molter spamming.
They have snipers.
>> Attack helicopters with hel with mini
guns and rockets.
What is this? All out warfare.
Crazy.
I like it's better if I reset.
>> Oh my god. Yeah.
>> I'm down over here.
>> Behind you. Just move.
He has been reviving me so much.
Wish you can like see everything else if
you're like
stole some stuff
from me.
He's reviving me. Okay.
Going to revive him.
I'll be the revive guy.
Crazy.
[__] you.
going to be the revive guy.
And I died.
Come on. Anyone?
I give you $500, please.
>> Jesus Christ. Somebody get me out.
>> Why are you looting me?
I gave you $500. Come on, just revive.
Okay, someone's reviving me.
Oh my lord. Holy m What the hell?
Yeah, I have 30. I earned $30,000
from this match
profit.
Stop sniping me.
Okay,
I played cool. Play it safe.
They have nothing.
Nothing.
if I'm if if it's possible or not. I
would like to just
I would like to just
go behind the enemy and
um like
electrocute him with a defab.
That will be crazy to imagine.
Just find the sniper now.
Snipe that. I don't have a sniper.
Was
he not here?
I hear him. I hear him. I hear him.
On top. On top. On top.
He's here. He's here.
Huh?
m snipe. That is a big snip. What the
hell? I was trying to zap him, bro. Come
on. A
why did you snipe me from 545 mashi?
That is just sad.
>> My most valued customer, you got to
spend money to make.
Look at my helicopter here.
Look at him.
Look at him go. So,
I need the
I have a parachute. Right. Okay. This
guy has a minigun.
This is a minigun chopper.
I feel like he's going to attack
along with this.
Wish I could like support him, you know.
That is the thingy for him to pew pew.
Damn, look at his crazy kills.
Oh my god, they're targeting us.
Crazy piloting skills.
Oh, he just dodged the missile.
Ah, never mind.
Ah, these guys.
Where was it? Where was it? This way.
Here.
Bro, those guys are having their RPGs
out and be like, "Yeah, I'm going to
kill people."
>> What are you looking for?
Anytime.
>> I'm going to make my money back.
I'll just deploy here.
That's way better. cheaper.
Um, if I play this game daily by now, I
would have unlocked uh like if I had
like 90 hours in this game, I would have
unlocked like um M4, the FA, Val, all
those higher grade weapons.
Enemy
bird in the air.
I came from here now. Oh yeah, let me go
hunt those rocket launcher people with
their car.
Oh, there's a tower here.
Where are they?
There's someone on the tower.
He know he know this man didn't
Who shot me all here?
>> Oh my god, they're shooting me.
At least I'm getting money for just
scouting these helicopters.
I got Who is here?
Where?
Uh huh.
Who is shooting?
>> Hostile vehicle taken out.
I can like kill them.
Stupid fool.
>> Target wiped.
Hostile. Up for additional contacts.
Ah, they had another guy.
Oh, wait. My internet is bad. Why?
I don't
>> [groaning]
>> My internet is bad again.
I'm burnt out of nowhere.
My game pinning thing is high.
Okay, we are live again. Hello.
We're alive again. My internet is bad
again. I don't know. Out of nowhere, it
just became like
Yeah, I'm back. I'm back. Out of
nowhere, it just went zero bit rate.
out of out of nowhere that just
happened. Wow.
Crazy.
>> Make it quick.
Come back anytime.
>> My favorite customer.
>> What if I don't buy
Okay, I just buy a simple load out and
just try to kill one,
but the game is going to get over.
One thing I understood is I have to get
this recon the binoculars or the
uh spy glass. Not spy glass, the the
recon
glass stuff.
That is important. Without that it's
hard.
Won't my dead body while be here? My my
my that box
stuff I died over here right
the shop
helicopter. Of
course, it's a sniper.
Of course though, it's a sniper.
all alone here.
Why? What is he doing?
want to get killed though.
One thing I could do is like be a be a
scouting guy.
Yeah, just take that this thing and then
wait 18 repairs.
Uhhuh.
Where the damn thing, bro.
The player from the server has been
permanently banned for cheating.
Oh, got it.
Damn.
What is the situation?
Why is there no one?
The hell?
Why no one's repairing the SCP? What is
going on?
No one's repelling the recipe.
I need it done.
Any
return helicopters? Hel? No.
Oh, he bought a helicopter.
The thing is I don't have a bad shot.
But this was a good street.
It is not.
Maybe this.
Oh my god.
Damn, he escaped but I died.
>> Now the question is, will he revive me?
>> I need some [__] help over here.
>> Damn, he escaped.
>> Left me hanging. Not even going to come
here.
ived me, I would have
gotten so much money just by scouting
the area. This guy is scouting, not even
moving.
Aha.
Bish.
Why is it going downhill though?
What?
I This is really bad.
>> [groaning]
>> It's buffering.
I mean, this makes me want to end so
bad.
I got to restart my stream again.
My game is over.
This is bad. This is SP.
I'm going
uh
it is lagging.
I hate it.
This is not This is not it.
It configuration file jitter upload
great stream buffering
bit rate increase to 800 waiting going
back to previous decrease to 200
ADV stream advancing switcher. Maybe
this guy
does it automatically check
for retreat.
There you go. They're coming.
Uh,
I'm talking about gun.
Hey, what if I do this? I make a macro
a macro.
Add F
if betrayed BB.
Uh, add obvious status.
Extreme betrayed us
below
below, thousand
then notification.
No
play audio
system.
Uh web socket window
system
betray is
low as [__]
Uh,
>> let me see if I can see.
Stream bit is low. Okay.
I need to
make this guy run on
run on
top of the notification.
Top of the notification. And I need the
do not disturb mode.
Set priority notifications.
Add apps.
Choose an app.
I want to add I want to add
this card. I want to add OBS.
Let's see
how it works.
Uh,
is it possible to vibableize it
only when perform actions
result changes?
I'm trying to debug this command name
now.
Uh
huh.
variable
coin script
uh profile loop log. Okay. File tonight.
How do I
Oh, wait. I can have a se uh text
source.
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah.
Can have a text source. Make it
stream bit rate is low
like this.
Then we add a gradient.
like this. Okay,
let me cook stream bit rate
betray
thingy
and I go to tools
advancing switcher
low bit
low bit Great.
Um, and I have a scene item visibility
uh on main.
This will be
game clean and it has to be this
that transition to
quality.
Uh it'll be show. Yeah.
If the thing is that
or not.
How do I add one more step into this?
Okay. Set condition input settings.
Uh this section allows you to specify
specific variables.
Okay.
I don't know what I will
I have to do for this.
How do I do available
trait?
Okay. Uh,
and if
I did this
again.
Uh
and uh F.
What is source interaction sequence
script? Okay. Anyway, I'll group it as
bit I just I wrote it as birth rate.
What the hell?
Okay. Um, that should do it.
>> Export.
What? I don't know.
action with the world qu. Okay,
I'm on a tight schedule, mate, so make
this quick.
I'll level up my recon.
>> I need a parachute.
There you go.
Let's go.
I'll be here chat. be a bit
All sides. All sides.
>> [groaning]
>> Okay, I'm back. I'm back. So
get there.
Foreign
A free backpack.
I get my
inventory is okay. Okay, nice. But
that's not the issue.
I'm not
Where's that?
Okay, let's save this.
Okay.
Rate normal tunn
about 10,000 betrayed. Okay. Wait,
Thank you. More
They're just building another
reverse Hey,
spotter.
What? Where is my spotter?
Oh my god, somebody stole it.
Adorable.
Oh.
>> [groaning]
>> Ah, he sniped me.
>> [screaming]
>> Okay.
Oh god, this guy is tacked.
Wow.
This guy has a rocket launcher.
What then? Let me just eat something.
Heat. Heat.
Get out of here.
[groaning]
>> [groaning]
>> Okay, I'm back. I'm so sorry. I'm still
alive, right? Okay, I'm still alive. Oh
god.
Uh,
I meant to I meant to make some noodles.
>> I was hungry. Guess you won't make money
hanging around here. Go on, treat them
back any time.
>> Shot.
Oh, blue team is winning. her email.
The blue dream.
Oh, he left.
Somebody here check me.
Okay, I'm coming.
It's all
this bulldog
is so quick.
Thanks so much.
Uh, the guy just killed me from here.
Also, this is where I
died earlier, right?
Wait, where did I die earlier?
Sit tight. I'm inbound.
Ah,
he's on top. What the hell?
I don't see
[groaning]
Thank you.
I was using a
Sam.
Oh, it's using a sound.
I'm just AFKing because I'm eating.
Assuming I get better.
of course you're All right.
Someone is actually away.
>> [groaning]
[groaning]
>> You must do
Can I talk you?
Wait,
actually.
Alex won't do it together.
We both get the XP
for our comrade who's over here.
I don't know.
An enemy supply point.
Where is everyone?
>> [groaning]
>> Bro, I died inside the wall.
What
the hell?
No one had just died like that.
What?
Ah, the game is going to end soon. Okay,
after this game,
I have to do a network test.
Enemy
nearby. Stay alert.
Bro, my game crashed.
You have no idea how the game is frozen.
What?
What? What? What?
Hold on. I'm inbound.
Aren't they
parameter?
We need help.
They're camping. There are four people
in a bunker bed or something. Bro,
[screaming]
what is this
Kyle?
He's
looting me.
He's taking me as prisoner.
Oh man.
Okay,
there's one teammate who is nearby. Just
wait for him.
Yeah.
M that
[groaning]
stream betray us. What
was that?
>> [groaning]
>> Oh, thank you for the follow. Avoid
matter 22 and anito lily.
Thank you. Thank you.
Mhm.
If it's below,000
maybe.
Isn't that better?
>> [groaning]
>> Oh.
What Okay.
And just use orbs.
rather than nitro.
Wait,
does how does this go natural work?
What the
profile.
Uh
uh
this game is a lost hope to come back
anytime. Why we need to spend money
bro?
Uh,
what the
edit profile
I'll just go here.
Why is the thing running all the time?
My bit rate was not low. The hell?
Uh
foundations are true.
okay. What the
whole PC is lagging. I hate this.
I really much hate this.
Let's
say
only
features There is
normal
And there this thing is over.
You know what? Yeah, let's go switch to
talking stream. Okay, for a bit.
This isn't working.
There's a lot of technical issues
happening and it's making me not want to
uh do this.
Why is there a spam full of things?
Okay, at least I understood the stuff I
[music] need to uh fix. So, I'll just do
that.
probably got the
thank you.
It's still running. Wait, the bit rate
is still 6,000. Why are you saying it's
low as [__] What?
What?
I shouldn't have used advancing
switcher, man. It's spamming.
Yeah, this thing is good, but
not not the way I want it to be.
F obvious stats
stream bit rate is below 2,000 bit rate
below. Okay. Below
below
below and it's supposed to do the same
visibility, the thing you saw earlier,
the stream bit rate thingy and then the
system tray notification thingy.
Wait until transmission is complete.
So, you know what? I'm kind of not want
to do the system tray thingy.
I had an idea.
I had an idea. Let me tell you my idea.
I want to send
like a phone notification like a HTTP
or some kind of
thingy to like
um to like
to my phone maybe or like trigger like
an alarm or something or like an alert.
my stream bit is low or if it's downward
or something that'll be better if I'm
correct.
Yeah, go if I'm bringing up technical
things but
like it is necessary for me to know
because of my Wi-Fi is unstable
currently. I switched it from 5G to 4G
so it's more stable and stuff.
The main issue I realized is always the
bit rate. My not bit rate the upload
speed. Upload speed is currently 10.
Sometimes you know on a good day good uh
good uh range day uh it becomes 20.
Yeah since 6 MP will be used from OBS
and rest of the MP will be used by the
game. It feels like too much, right?
Then my roommate will be uh using his
phone or watching um like
movies or anime or using his Mac book or
something or to work or something that
will also consume network and there'll
be network throttling.
Yeah,
I'm like thinking in my mind like
imagine
if I get my second PC all build it,
right?
um if I'm able to bring the parts from
India somehow and [music] then um buy
like a good net or like a secondhand cab
full TX cabinet and put the motherboard
and everything and set up everything
and get everything done and put it put
that PC case underneath my desk or
something or top of the desk or
whatever. Right. Then um then the issue
is if my stream is like acting up like
this, right?
Um
if my stream is acting up like this,
um it'll just cause issues.
Why is because I would have to always
keep an eye.
That also means that I have to keep have
a second monitor or something, right?
Which I don't have.
Uh
hold on.
Yeah, I went to a PC shop today
actually. I mean uh went to a PC shop
and I I scouted for all the prices
for like PC case,
uh motherboard,
um and like what power supply
Japanese um PC storage they they um sell
like a lot of modular power supplies. is
rather than normal ones.
Yeah. And modular ones are always
expensive.
It is always expensive.
Yeah. So yeah, I checked the cooler, PC
cooler, CPU, CPU cooler stuff, power
supply, everything.
They have this kind of, how do I say
this? They have, it's not like a big TV
screen or like a monitor monitor. They
have a mini monitor.
Um, if I were to give an example, it's
like your pencil box.
which you have you can take for
uh academic stuff. Yeah, it's like a
small thingy but more like a rectangular
like a
it's like a lunch box. [snorts]
A lunch box.
Small one. There's like um more how do
you say? It's like almost the size of a
keyboard. Yeah. Yeah. There's a monitor
which is literally a size of a keyboard,
literally a keyboard, rectangular
monitor kind of thingy to display.
And I'm like wondering in my mind like h
this is nice.
I kind of do want to get it but I don't
know.
Cuz
currently if I'm um going for the
cheaper route, I do have a TV kind of
allin-one thingy. It has a television
thingy and also it has a HDMI thingy
like a old television or monitor kind of
thingy. not monitor television all in
one thingy I have
um in my apartment on my dometry it came
with this TV kind of thingy so I'm
thinking of using that as my second
monitor when second monitor or uh I'm
thinking of using it as a monitor when
my streaming PC will fully set it up and
build what's got it yeah I'm kind of
ending cuz u I had to eat and Um, I've
been AFK and it's always it's already
going to be 12
D
really
George for HD. Thank you for the follow
and kick. Thank you for coming in.
Thank you. Thank you.
How's the Roku doing?
Hope you've been well.
Not
today and tomorrow and after tomorrow a
silver week.
So, tomorrow now I [music] I know I can
stream after coming back from work, but
maybe I won't do that. Oh my god. Thank
you for donating your membership
on YouTube, Roku.
I think membership prices kind of
increased cuz YouTube being YouTube
wanted to keep it at 29 rupees but I
think it's increased a little bit. I
don't know how much is the current price
if you want to hide
I have to
there's so many things that I can't I'm
super broke this month this is right I
have to pay my uh school and do stuff
and so many deadlines of payments
And I'm like, "Yeah, boy. My salary is
really less this month cuz August I took
a few leave like uh I was absent from
work because of my birthday, this and
that. Um I was I had fever, this and
that. And now I'm facing the aftermath
of [music] not going for work even if it
was for 4 hours or 3 hours. Yeah. Bye.
But yeah, it is what it is.
But yeah,
what is it there for tomorrow? Let's
let's see what's my schedule looking
tomorrow. Tomorrow I come from work like
at what uh 12 of work it's over. I come
straight here as a one or two. Then I
could probably
Okay,
I could probably
uh I have to I have to do like a video
thinging to do like a recording for
something. I have to do that.
After that,
um
after that I'm kind of free, but I do
wanted to go to this uh re like there's
this shop called Hard Off.
Uh that's a store where everything is
second or used products which are
getting sold
good quality stuff which are getting
sold like you get like anime figurines
have a lot of things like that on a hard
off store in Japan. So I want to go
there and like look take pictures or
prices of components for P computer.
Um especially like what I'm think I need
to have is like a DVI
display port DP to HD DP to USB
uh thingy [music] thingy I think. No,
no, no. DP to HDMI, then HDMI to USB
thingy. That's what I need. Wait, was it
was
what the
uh it's a HVM [music]
in. So, I think I can plug my HDMI on
this.
Can uh do input HDMI input. I know
output I can do. Okay. Okay.
though. I might have to buy have to do
buy like an HDMI cable or maybe I can do
it later when I get my components from
India.
As long as my um as long as I can get
the capture card, the GPU motherboard,
everything it's good.
And uh
but as I said like the current issue is
the Wi-Fi current on 4G connection right
now the network um type is 4G not uh 5G
um 5G bit rate is kind of unstable but
4G seems stable. I [music] you know I
was not streaming on my like I was not
sending the stream to YouTube, Twitch,
kick, um Rumble and Twitter five
platforms or four platforms.
Uh 3, four, five. Yeah, five platforms.
But I was sending the feed to Multimill
and Caster Labs.
So I uh figured out a way. So I sent one
output to Caster Labs. So, I pay $4 for
that and sent it to the Singapore
server.
One would say, "Doc, you can just buy
the $7 thingy and just send YouTube,
Twitch, kick, rumble, Twitter from
guess, right?" But I was like, "Ah, I
could, but I don't want to. I want to
use the free version of Multimill."
Same developer at the show, different
company, but yeah, same developer. gas
labs people work through for me
multimold so but they don't multi
doesn't have a Singapore server so the
main issue is from Japan to Sydney or
London is too much ping so I have to
send to a Sydney server and the Sydney
server will relay the feed to the uh no
Singapore server will relay the feed to
Sydney
yeah the only downside of this setup is
I'll not be able to uh do a vertical
stream like short stream on YouTube like
give a different output.
So the
only disadvantage
but it's okay it's all right.
Yeah.
What could I
too much things in my brain right now?
I'm like I I was like uh today earlier
um one of the viewers on um
Olaron was uh saying that he found my
donation page on Google. I it redirected
him to my website thingy. And talking
about website, it just reminded me there
was a new update for web studio
where you
you make MDX file. You can use chat GPT
and the MCN thingy to web studio MCN to
like generate blog stuff. So it can
they're they're they made it so modular.
It's so good. current my current stuff
is like my my website's guideline page
and everything is hard hardcoded I guess
as in I go to the project file in web
[music] studio open it and I for each
line is like a text div thingy right
[music] but if I convert that to an MDX
file I just have to edit the file that's
it I can add image everything they made
like a visual builder too, like a visual
debtor for the MDX file. And that's so
good. It's like you can make a blog post
thing, you know? Oh my god, I'm I know
I'm yapping so much when it comes to
these stuff, but
I I want to do that. I want to fix that.
Ya.
All I have to do is update the MDX file
now. That's so convenient to show and my
automated stuff with notion that too I
can like bind it or say make stuff like
connected and I
Yeah. And right now like the bit obvious
betray thing you know I just got an
idea. Oh, I was after the stream I was
like thinking of asking Chad GBD like is
there a way I can somehow send a HTTP
HTTP request or a web soocket request or
something
to my phone or maybe to like Google uh
assistant or whatever or if
a web hook or something
and it triggers some uh like an event
and it [music] sends like uh event data
saying your OBS bit rate is below
1,000 bit rate and it makes it like uh
sends the alert to my phone and it does
like an alarm or like a timer or
something or like a one or sound effect
or something.
Nah, cuz if it's if if I have a sound
effect of it on my PC, I won't no I mean
laptop, I won't recognize if I'm playing
a game with my phone buzzing and
alerting me just like an earthquake
alert here, which happens here often in
Japan. Um sometimes um yeah, if uh yeah,
if if that was if that's possible, that
would be so nice, mirror. Oh my god,
that will be so nice.
No, cuz I need to know that like today I
was like, "Oh, my internet will be
fixed. It's uh stable." I yesterday
streamed for like yesterday did not go
public stream but like privately tested
streaming
uh for
18 hours. [music]
I think day before yesterday I did the
testing switched from five 5G to 4G. uh
changed like so many things and um I
realized that
the issue was the hello white matter 22
welcome welcome
hello
we're just yapping we're done with the
game for today for tonight
we yapping
welcome And
welcome.
Uh, where was I? Um, what the
where was I?
Where was I? Oh my god.
Wait, where was
what was the thing? Oh my god, I just
forgot. ADHD.
But yeah, anyway, um
we got
I have stuff I have to fix
lately. Now, my Warog streams are like
full of technical issues
like uh recently I messed messed around
with the in-game uh kind of or engine
files to make everything low, super low
so that my laptop can bear wet
when I'm multiing and when I'm streaming
cuz my My gaming laptop is handling
everything now like streaming
uh streaming from my laptop and then
playing the game. Too much resources,
right? Got to go. Love your stream. Ah,
thank you. Thank you. Thank you.
Have a good one. Thank you for chatting.
Thank you.
Hi. Um
always issues
technical issues and I hate these.
I want to be free from this.
more
but I I have higher expectation
um towards like I I know uh even if I
have expectations but uh there will be
not a way there won't be a place where I
won't have issues or technical issues if
even if I am on a dual PC setup
but Yeah,
but all I can say is like if I'm
switching to a dual pieces setup, the
load will be lighter. I'm just have to
make sure if I'm strictly gaming, I use
the stream page here. If I'm not
strictly gaming,
I switch to this P gaming laptop OBS
game OBS I can call it or main OBS
which is this one I'm streaming right
now right
if you're doing if we are doing like
music stuff if you if we are doing
anything other [music] desktop kind uh
desktop based streams
here home like where I'm home and like
sit seated it down. Yeah, that those
stuff we can go with the normal one and
whenever I need
the need to balance the load then I can
give it to the game p uh stream PC.
Yeah, that's my idea for now. Oh,
so this
also it is 12. We can slowly wrap up
now. Hi.
Regarding tomorrow's stream, I'll keep
you guys updated. I do want to try out
Fortnite, but feel like I'll try it out
next week. Next week I have like a one
week vacation
though I won't be would be be able to
like stream all day but
at least uh wait Sunday I might have to
go to Shinjuku though but Saturday at
least this coming Saturday at least I'll
try to
do a longer stream this week last
weekend like uh last Saturday and Sunday
I could not stream longer hour more than
2 hoursish
um which is my fault for like being too
tired and falling asleep and not being
wake up able to wake up
um was body pain everything didn't want
to stream
but
yeah this [music] weekend
let's see I can make it happen
cuz um yeah feel like next month the war
dogs is going to reset and
everything will be back to zero.
Yeah, everything will be back to zero
and that's kind of bad and not bad more
like it is what it is but yeah and
yeah thank you for watching today. Thank
you to all who came by today. All the
people who came by today are Ruru. Thank
you for coming by. Thank you for the
YouTube membership renewal and also
welcome to the astral constellation on
both YouTube and Twitch. Thank you.
Thank you to Solarum for the $2
donation. Thank you on Kofi. Thank you
so much.
Then George for HD, thank you for the
follow on kick.
Anita Lily, thank you for the follow on
Twitch. Void Matter 22, thank you for
the follow on Twitch.
Welcome to all the newcomers. Thank you.
My name is Ch Next. I'm an Indian
consolation YouTuber
currently in Japan
after my dreams
for shining the brightest.
Thank you for watching. Dishan
came by today. Thank you.
And uh Roku,
that's everyone who came by.
Wait, if you are lurking, thank you for
lurking.
Really means a lot.
So fun.
over the stream. Um, right now it's
stable
and it's only, how do I say this?
It's only a four or 5 second delay.
That's really low latency and better.
And yeah, um, I hope uh when I'm doing
streams or game streams, it's become
stabilized like this.
And if there's a way to make
backend stuff to make it more better,
I'll try to do it. Got some ideas which
are just came into my brain right now
this very second. [music] I'm going to
do that. Bye. Thank you again Mina for
coming by today. I'll see you guys in
the next one. Come. Bye-bye. Good night.
May the stars bless you tonight and
guide you and look after you and grant
you your
good dream tonight. What's to talk?
Bye-bye. Talk next time.